

Enrique Zetina

Software Developer

+52 1 55 22 86 69 19



www.ezetina.com



linkedin.com/in/ezetina



github.com/ezetina86



platzi.com/@ezetina



jenzetin@gmail.com

About me ——

Data engineer with extensive experience in OraclePL/SQL and cloud computing (GPC). Curious and goal-oriented, very good learning and teaching new technologies and collaborating with team members. Has a Bachelor degree in Computer Engineering and Oracle DBA certification.

Skills

PL-SQL 90%

Java 70%

Linux administration 70%

Google Cloud Platform 65%

[Goal oriented, excellent technical skill, ability to solve problem quickly, team spirit]

Languages —

English 80%

Spanish Native

Education

2006-2013 Bachelor of Computer Technology

Antivirtus and Antispam system implemented in a FPGA.

Certifications

2014 ORACLE Administration Workshop IPN ESIME.

2014 ORACLE SQL Fundamentals

Latest Courses

Architecting with Google Cloud Platform Specialization Coursera.
Artificial Intelligence Foundations: Machine Learning Linkedin Learning.

2019 Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals Xentrica.

2018 Java EE Professional course E-learning Platzi.

Experience

2019-Present Big Data Support Engineer.

EPAM Systems

UAM Azc.

IPN ESIME.

Google Mexico

Provide support to customers using Cloud Platform products, solutions and APIs, including Big Data and related services.

Identify and document product bugs and feature requests and work with internal support teams as well as customers to implement effective solutions.

I work closely with internal support teams to improve cloud products at a senior level.

Working with Big Data technology (Hadoop, MapReduce, HDFS). Writting code using programming languages as Java and Python. Working with NoSQL databases and big data querying tools like Pig, Hive, Impala.

2018-2019 Oracle Developer

4th Source

ESI(Express Scripts) Working on transformation team, developing PL/SQL code to migrate existing systems to new platforms, in this position, I'm getting lots of experience in Java and tools like Kafka and Attunity.

Developing PL/SQL.

Developing web services using Java EE.

Work with tools like Kafka, Zookeeper, Attunity.

2017-2018 Oracle Senior Developer

AsTec

Banco Azteca, member of the team that developed a project called MER, who identified elements that could cause risk on branches, the purpose was to measure risks to take actions and avoid fines.

Devolping PL/SQL code to webapps.

Desing database model to support MER system.

Code functions, procedures, views, sequences, indexes and data model to interact with Frontend and Backend.

2016-2017 Business expansion expert

Telefónica

Devolping KPI's for openings.

Desing and implentation from software soutions mainly using ORACLE PL/SOL.

Dashboard developing to monitor new openings.

Reengineering of existing process in order to have better control of

sales and incomes.